SURELY TOMORROW
-You're a journalist for Dongwoon Daily?
-Yes.
-Do you really know each other?
Ms. Seo Ji-woo, are you sure you know him?
Not sure. Maybe?
"Maybe?"
One second. Fine.
Here, look at this.
JARIM APPAREL
SEO JI-WOO
We do know each other.
Then why take her luggage...
That's what I mean.
I had something to say to her,
but she avoided me.
Something important.
I don't have anything to say.
Hey.
What?
What is it that you have to say?
Is running away your specialty?
What I'm saying is…
Is this the right time
to run away to England?
Why do you care?
Whether I slack off here
or on the London Bridge in England,
it's up to me.
I'm saying that's a very selfish mindset.
Get it? Here's an example.
Your sister and her company, you know?
It's hard to run it.
Yet you're going around wasting money?
Why not stay and learn something?
You're being so damn nosy.
Anyway, I have to go back to work.
Let's talk again later.
-Are you serious?
-I am.
What about the flight I missed
because of you?
That's--
7.2 million won, first class.
How are you going to make up for that?
Why the first class?
-Pay me.
-Me?
Yes, you. You held me back.
I put my house on the market
and got rid of everything.
I hate to go back there,
so I'm staying at your place.
My place? Why? Just go to a hotel.
Oh, are you paying for the hotel as well?
I'm getting a suite.
If you just go back to your--
Shut up. It's either the ticket price
or the door code to your house.
Your account number.
Nuri Bank. 345864830.
-Too fast. Say that again.
-345864830.
Sent. Bye. We're not done talking yet.
NURI BANK
WIRE TRANSFER
1,121 won?
Never seen such a number in my account.
What the hell? What a lunatic…
You wanted the code.
Oh, the door code.
SURELY TOMORROW
EPISODE 3
Yes, well, Ji-woo's in my house.
Somehow it happened.
You should pick her up and…
What?
If I step in, it'll all be ruined.
It will look like I'm snooping around her.
And if I tell her that
I asked you to help, it'll only get worse.
It is what it is.
Oh, I have a meeting to attend now. Bye.
These women…
Is this a setup?
I couldn't even check in, Se-yeong.
What? Kyeong-do showed up at the airport?
Kyeong-do? Put it on speaker. The speaker.
-Oh, wait. Ouch, that hurts.
-Gosh! Be careful!
He stopped me from leaving.
Next in line.
Don't go, Ji-woo.
But we're no longer together.
I can't let you go like this.
Kyeong-do.
Come with me.
So where are you now?
Me? I'm at Kyeong-do's place.
Kyeong-do's place?
-She's at Kyeong-do's place.
-But why?
Oh, I don't know.
He told me to wait for him at his house.
He said he didn't want to leave me alone
in my house or whatever.
You should go back to work.
Where will you be?
I'll be home and lonely…
One, one, two, one.
You and me, the two of us,
become one again.
That's the door code to my place.
You being lonely in that house again?
I can't bear to see it.
Please go to my place.
Okay.
SEO JI-WOO
A green light?
Jeez, Kyeong… Gosh. Kyeong…
Kyeong-do is such a romantic, huh?
So romantic. I think he learned that
from me. Hey, hold on.
Oh, my gosh!
Hey, Woo-sik.
I heard you made a scene at the airport
to stop Seo Ji-woo today, you goof!
Me? At the airport? What?
Huh? What?
Oh, Woo-sik. I'm hanging up.
I feel like puking. Bye.
Why would she change the story like that?
Is she out of her mind?
This is so stressful, jeez.
Hey, were you going to England
to study Shakespeare?
Why did you change the story…
What? Study sex in England?
Are you nuts?
Did you drink all that by yourself…
Do you want one?
Hey.
Hey. Get up now.
This isn't a bar. What are you doing?
Go to your house.
I'll send you 7.2 million, so go now.
Hey, by the way…
This stinks. It smells...
weird.
Take it off.
Why are you telling me to strip?
You're hopeless. Let's go now. Get up.
I'm not going anywhere! You stopped me.
-Why don't you join me?
-No, I don't want to.
What? Why are you raising your voice?
Are you worked up, Kyeong-do?
Jeez. Get a grip, will you?
I did.
So, let's talk.
Why did you come to stop me?
When you heard that I was leaving,
did you feel…
feel... like...
Were you sad? Is that it?
We'll talk when you're sober.
Get changed first.
Gosh, you keep telling me to…
Fine, I'll take it off.
Hey, come on.
I didn't tell you to get changed here.
Why are you like this?
Huh? What…
Hey, wait.
Hey, what are you doing? Hold on.
Oh, my Kyeong-do, you pookie.
You're still so handsome,
aren't you? Right?
Hey, stop…
SPRING 2007
Take the rooms today instead of the hall.
All rooms are full.
Oh, okay.
That's funny.
Ji-woo, are you okay?
Oh, no.
Ji-woo, when are you going back
to the States?
When your semester begins?
She's going back soon.
You seem to be losing weight.
Ji-woo, are you on a diet?
She eats well and sleeps well,
but she's not gaining any weight.
Oh, no.
You won't be back for a while.
Let me get you some oriental medicine.
Sir, would you like to try the wine first?
No need to try. I'll just take it.
Ji-woo, let's go to the restroom.
Excuse us. We're going to the restroom.
Is this where you work on the weekends?
Yes.
Are you having a family dinner?
Oh, then is your school…
Who's this?
Oh, hello.
Ji-woo's friend?
Oh, yes.
Since when? I don't recognize--
Mom, Kyeong-do is my--
Oh, one of my friends is her friend, so…
We've only said hi.
Ma'am, is there something you need?
Will you change the server in charge?
Yes, ma'am.
It'll be uncomfortable
when we're here to enjoy dinner.
A mere part-timer in a VIP room?
It doesn't sound right, does it?
Well... have a great evening.
Oh, this way...
Ji-woo, let's go.
Everyone is waiting.
You know the chairman's daughter?
-The chairman?
-JARIM Apparel.
The head office of Indiago.
Didn't you know about your friend?
WRITE A MESSAGE
HEY, KYEONG-DO...
Did you eat yet?
Let's go eat.
Come on. Let's grab something to eat.
I'm sorry, Kyeong-do.
Ji-woo.
Your feelings for me are real, right?
Why are you bringing that back?
I mean, it upsets me
when I think about it.
What does?
That I'm delivering my son
his dress shirts at this age.
Tell him to get them himself.
Had an argument with Deacon Lee?
Why did you get changed?
Embarrassed now that you're sober?
Get me one too.
-Do you even remember?
-Yes.
Think about why you
did something you'd regret.
It's all alcohol.
I wouldn't jump at anyone
just because I'm drunk.
I'm glad to hear that I'm not just anyone.
Was it romantic?
You carried me to the bed.
-I threw you.
-Bullshit. I said I remember everything.
Why did you stop me?
You know Ji-woo.
She's full of energy.
But what makes me sad
is that all that energy
is making her depressed.
It was hard for Ji-woo to get divorced
because of her depression and alcoholism.
But if she finds out about this,
that I'm going blank due to Alzheimer's…
Then Ji-woo will probably…
This is frustrating.
Ji-woo must not know that I'm sick.
Here's what I think.
This is your chance
to redefine your identity before 40.
But you tried to run away again.
Like you did when you were 20 and 28.
New York or England, I wouldn't stop you
if you had a purpose.
What will you do in England?
Did you stop me to lecture me?
Look at all those cans you drank.
Just enough to die in England.
Even if you go,
you need to get a grip first.
Is that why you came running
to the airport?
I'm worried.
Is it love?
Do you want the car key?
Or do you want to call a taxi?
-Go home first and--
-No.
I'm going to leave anyway,
so why will I go back to that house?
It's a pain in the ass
to reset everything. No.
Did you listen to anything I said?
Going to England is not the point.
Did you stop me just to be a jerk?
I don't believe you. It was your feelings.
You didn't have a plan,
but you'd stop me anyway.
Your developing frontal lobe
brought those feelings back to you.
Is it too hard to understand?
Your nonsense isn't hard to understand,
it's just ridiculous.
Come home early. I'm bored.
I clock off sharp on time,
so get it together and go home.
We'll talk later.
You need to change the way you think.
Did you meet Aaron?
Briefly in Beijing.
The price is too low.
It's not my company,
but it'd leave us nothing.
-I think he's getting China involved.
-China?
It's an IT company.
They're interested in an apparel company
as big as JARIM.
Besides, Min-woo,
the price isn't what matters right now.
What matters is the time.
If this goes wrong,
both you and I are doomed.
You made me spend 30 billion won
to make a paper company.
Don't make me regret it.
We got rid of your brother-in-law,
that Cho Jin-eon guy.
When is it for your wife?
Soon. It won't be long.
One year maximum?
How long do you think
Seo Ji-yeon can hide it?
She's literally going,
"Where am I? Who am I?"
As soon as the news got out, it's done.
Just keep Aaron.
He's coming to Korea next month.
Let's meet him quietly.
What the heck?
What do you want for lunch?
The same place?
Sounds good to me.
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message…
You can only live in peace if you pick up.
Kang Min-woo.
They're in talks with a guy named Aaron.
A specialist
in buying and selling companies.
Bae Jun-soo said that a Chinese IT company
is interested in JARIM.
Does he meet up with Bae Jun-soo often?
No, maybe once a month?
They met at the tennis court today.
Okay. Thank you for your work.
You're excited because I'm sick.
Maybe she…
What?
Lee Kyeong-do, are you home?
What the heck?
Shoot.
I'm waiting for jokbal.
Don't get worked up, just wait.
I should just…
While getting jokbal,
you should've gotten makgeolli, too.
-Drink soda instead.
-Too much sugar.
Water. Drink water then.
Hey, still,
doesn't having someone at home feel…
Should I say, warm? You know?
No, I don't.
It's better than empty. You heard me
taking a shower, and you got jokbal.
What? What does you taking a shower
have to do with the jokbal?
Being a journalist made you a dick.
Nitpicking much?
You've been so idle
that you've lost all sense of reality.
You see the world like a child.
Bullshit. And you're so grown up
that you have jokbal with a child?
Whatever. Just eat your jokbal.
Where are you going again?
You're not going to your house.
I told you I can't.
So make yourself at home.
Imagine this is your house.
I'll waste my money at the sauna
and sleep uncomfortably.
Okay. But get changed every morning
before going to work.
We stink at that age.
That musty smell on a rainy day,
you know what I mean?
The musty smell? That's my favorite.
You said it was a lease.
You break, you fix. That's the law.
My landlord is cooperative.
Because someone died here,
he provides first-class service.
You like first class. Hope you enjoy.
That's scary. I'm scared of ghosts.
Shit. Lee Kyeong-do, that asshole.
If there are ghosts…
I'll stop them with alcohol.
SIKHYE
DONGWOON DAILY
Let's see…
Gosh.
Jeez.
I worked so hard to get a lease,
Seo Ji-woo took it over.
The well-off are worse.
Shit.
Still not coming?
Is he acting up, or being shy?
(FOR MEN)
Leave a text when you move out.
There are bugs in the food waste.
Better come home before they lay eggs.
The food waste card
is in the left sink drawer.
Clean up after you eat.
If the bugs lay eggs, stir-fry them.
So you're not coming home until I leave?
Are you serious?
By now, you're basically trespassing.
You're the one
who stopped me from leaving.
You're old enough to understand me now.
Seo Ji-woo, the trespasser.
Who's available on Thursday, the 16th,
at 1:00 p.m.?
I'll go.
But you're not available.
I'm not?
Check your schedule. Jeez.
Sorry.
Frozen shoulder, Kyeong-do?
It's andropause.
You should go, Assistant Manager Lee.
Damn it.
He's changed.
He's not innocent anymore.
JARIM Apparel?
That clothing company? That humongous one?
Why does that matter?
Hey, she doesn't go to this school.
Our club's identity relies on this matter!
Still, the club…
Ji-woo… Well, she missed the timing.
She wasn't trying to fool us or…
Wait, you're getting too close.
-You asshole...
-That means she's a semi-chaebol!
You sure spent money well.
You capitalist, money-crazed jerk.
That's not the point!
She has money, so--
Oh, shut up!
Shut up, you asshole.
I'm sorry.
Are we that cool?
Did you hide it to hang out with us?
What?
-She's kind of… yeah.
-Yes, yeah.
Then there's something we need to clarify.
You! That car.
You said it was your friend's.
Is it yours?
-Yes.
-You even have a car?
Hey, my father sells cars,
but I still don't have one--
Are you a good driver?
Well, no accident yet…
We should have a workshop
for our play, right?
What? Out of nowhere?
Did you say a workshop?
Why not? Isn't it perfect?
The workshop…
begins now.
Now? We're going now?
-Hey, a workshop!
-Are we going now?
Hey, wait…
Oh, I love it so much.
Jeong-min, can you do better
so I can feel the wind?
-This car is awesome!
-Ji-woo, can I borrow this for a week?
Do you want to sit in the trunk?
Nice. Let's go, let's go!
You deserve it, you idiot. Come here!
Chaos!
One, two, three, go!
One more time?
Wait.
I'm so happy.
One, two, three.
You're pushing me.
Ji-woo.
Do you want to go outside?
Oh… This is nice.
I love the sound of the waves.
It was a good idea to come.
I had so much fun today.
Ji-woo!
What are you doing here by yourself?
There's no one around.
Weren't you scared?
Search.
What?
I mean, there could be
a 500-won coin in here.
A 500-won coin?
Oh, hurry up and dig already.
What? A 500 won out of nowhere?
Hey, there's something my mom always says.
"Digging won't give you any coin."
That means you'll find no single coin.
Still, give it a try. You might find it.
I'll only get sand under my nails.
Well, how? Like this?
-Yes.
-Like this?
There's nothing… What's in here… Wait.
You hid it on purpose.
Wait, don't you recognize what it is?
It's 500 won.
No, do you know what that 500 won means?
-A 500-won coin with a hole.
-No.
It's the 500 won you lost.
The one you were looking for
in front of the School of Humanities.
What? Oh, yeah, right.
You had it all along?
Yes. I'll give it back to you
since that brought you to me.
So you've been keeping it.
You had it this whole time.
This is amazing.
Make sure to keep it
for a long time. Promise.
Okay.
I'll take this.
Sure. I'll get you a new item.
Thank you.
This is my dad's company…
But you worked so hard to make that money.
But I promised you.
Besides, I think they make nice clothes.
If you're going to buy clothes anyway,
it's killing two birds with one stone.
Sure, thank you.
Hey, I love the color.
-Really?
-Yes.
Did you pick this?
Of course.
And here.
What's this?
Huh?
Press here.
Kyeong-do.
It's a gift.
Our time together that 500 won brought us.
Don't forget that.
This is so pretty.
It's really pretty. I love it.
I'm glad.
I promise to cherish it.
Assistant Manager Lee, are you okay?
You're getting weaker every day.
It feels like you're rotting.
Andropause, he said.
Hey, how about some gopchang with cola?
Wow.
Oh, well… Let's talk outside.
I locked the gas.
And I vacuumed the place.
I didn't do the laundry, though.
It'd be a waste of water and detergent
if I only washed that one shirt.
You care about Earth now?
Oh. I ran out of underwear,
so I took one of yours.
-And I hand-washed that.
-You should've just thrown it out.
It was bittersweet to live together.
Bye.
No questions, please.
Why did she vacuum your place?
Why did she wear your underwear?
"Bittersweet" what?
What exactly happened?
Where are you going, Kyeong-do?
What the hell happened?
Don't cry.
Where are you going?
Oh, I couldn't take out the recycling.
Wouldn't taking out the recycling
need much less effort than this?
That maniac. Jeez,
I knew she was a lunatic. Seriously.
Mom. You scared me.
What is all this?
I didn't drink them.
Then where did you get them?
Are you drinking again?
No.
No, right?
Did you take it for refunds?
Are you out of money?
Oh, it's my friend.
He drank so much
so I'm taking them out for him.
Your friend left without cleaning up?
I admit that this is suspicious,
but it wasn't me. It really wasn't.
I can never stand that twice. You know?
Doesn't the Bible
say something about doubt?
Besides, why'd you take this route
to the store?
To watch you, you brat!
Bye, Mom.
I didn't drink any of them. I swear.
Again. They're at a disadvantage again.
And now, here, before the ball goes
any further in, it's caught.
With the second base vacant,
the ball is passed…
Be careful on your way home.
And don't fight!
-Bye!
-Bye-bye.
NAMU ART ACADEMY
Jeez, if you were going to fight,
why did you even stay together?
He always starts it first.
Gosh, now that he's older,
he's so twisted.
So? Did you move out?
Yeah.
Are you going to England?
-Yeah.
-Why don't you just stay?
Do you want me to stay here too?
That'd be nice. Then I'll get to see
your pretty face every day.
Do you think
that's why Kyeong-do stopped me?
He wouldn't have stopped you
if he hated you.
He did nothing when I threw myself at him.
You threw yourself at him?
Well, I just gave it a try.
To see how he feels about me.
If he still…
I just pulled a prank.
There should be a thesis about you two.
You guys are weird.
What did you do at his place
when he wasn't even home?
Oh, I just drank.
It seems Kyeong-do doesn't drink anymore.
Or he stayed sober
so he wouldn't fall for me?
Kyeong-do doesn't drink.
Why not? Does he have a liver problem?
Ji-woo.
When you meet Kyeong-do again,
don't drink.
Kyeong-do…
Something happened?
He was treated for alcoholism
over a long time.
Hospitalized for quite a while.
He almost got fired from work.
When?
When did that happen?
Back then… when you left…
He endured it when he was 20.
But when you left for the second time,
he crumbled.
Ji-woo!
You aren't kind. You're just stupid.
When an idiot goes nuts, it's hopeless.
Are you drunk?
Keep your damn head off me.
What? What is wrong with you?
Hey, Lee Kyeong-do.
Alcohol, alcohol, alcohol!
I wondered why you went on about it.
What, alcoholism?
That only appears in movies.
Why… Why you?
You're making a fuss over nothing.
"Nothing"?
You were hospitalized,
and almost got fired. That's nothing?
What do you want me to do then?
It just happened.
I just drank,
and ended up doing it every day.
It happened before I knew it.
That's why I told you to stop drinking
in case you end up like me.
And it's all in the past.
There's no need to get upset.
Why did you drink?
I don't know. I don't even remember.
Why did you drink so much?
Why? What do you want me to say?
You drank because of me.
Jeez.
It wasn't because of anyone.
I just boozed up because I liked it.
You...
You never blame me even a little.
That pisses me off even more.
I was a bitch to you,
but you say you just liked it?
I drank because I was frustrated.
That's all!
I tried walking, and I tried running!
But nothing helped me understand!
So I drank, happy?
I just couldn't get it.
Why you left me like that.
Back then and even now,
I just don't get it.
Hey.
If you were going to leave me…
if you were going to leave me like that…
you shouldn't have come back!
You… you jerk.
Shit…
Seriously…
I'm getting dizzy.
I'm running out of energy
after hearing I'm a jerk.
Sorry about calling you a jerk.
Let's call it even.
I'm too tired to even fight back.
Oh, don't look at me like that.
It's frustrating.
How am I looking at you?
I don't know.
It's frustrating because I don't know.
I don't know what to do with that look.
It's because I want both of us
to get a grip.
Was it tough? I mean, the treatment.
Was it tough?
Yes.
Just how much did you drink
to be hospitalized?
I'm telling you, if you drink like that,
there's no other way. So quit.
I will. So you should also…
Ji-woo.
When you think about it,
we didn't even date for a whole year.
But perhaps…
Maybe I'm too soft.
I guess I couldn't let it go.
I couldn't move on.
It's all in the past.
So I'm embarrassed to get so angry.
Did you eat?
Yes.
-Let's go. I'll walk you to your car.
-It's fine.
Now you're finally getting a grip.
You know what, Kyeong-do?
At the time, I was too…
I mean, it's not that I left you…
but I left to die.
But it was really frightening to die.
It felt like a dream
to see you at home
when I went home after work.
I'm sure you had your reasons.
But still,
you should've seen me before you left.
I have a favor to ask you.
Don't worry about me from now on.
Sorry about messing with you
in the last few days.
I think I finally pulled myself together.
It's no longer love.
And I'd be such a bitch
to call it a friendship.
So I just hope…
the best for you.
Bye.
It's no longer love.
And I'd be such a bitch
to call it a friendship.
Stop drinking and stop swearing,
you woman…
Seo Ji-woo.
Good decision.
Start learning the ropes.
I booked the ticket again.
I'm leaving soon.
Do you have itchy feet or something?
Why do you keep going abroad?
If you made a fuss over your divorce,
you need to show your next step.
Is my next step finding my spot
in the company?
Don't you know the situation you're in?
I do. I know it very well.
I guess one can't play dumb
unless they have the energy.
Am I your insurance?
Do you even qualify to be my insurance?
No shares whatsoever.
Seo Ji-woo, the illegitimate child.
You…
Since when did you know?
When I was 28.
I'm not Dad's, but you had an--
Shut your mouth!
Have you been pretending this whole time?
How despicable.
Despicable?
This is crazy.
Mom, why do you think
Dad cherished me so much?
I must've been an eyesore to him.
It's probably because he pitied me.
Because you disdained me like a bug,
he must've pitied the poor, innocent kid.
Let's talk again later.
No, I'm never going to see you again.
I'm not working at the company.
I'm not going to do that for you.
Dad's will that he'd give me the shares?
I don't care.
You used to yell at me
not to come back to Korea.
And now you want me to work here
to get my shares?
I'm not going to be your insurance.
Does...
Ji-yeon know?
Aren't you going to apologize to me?
How did you know?
Ji-yeon told me.
Are you afraid now?
Are you finally afraid?
SE-YEONG
-Yes, Se-yeong.
-Hey, Kyeong-do.
I thought Ji-woo was pretty shocked today,
so I came to her place to check on her.
And?
I hear the phone ringing inside,
but she won't open the door.
Hey, Seo Ji-woo!
Ji-woo!
-Call the locksmith.
-Okay.
Ji-woo!
Hello?
Hi, my door is locked.
Sir, can you come here as fast as you can?
Ji-woo!
Hey, Ji-woo, wake up, will you?
Ji-woo, wake up, please?
Ji-woo, come on. Seo Ji-woo!
SURELY TOMORROW
Honey, have you seen the watch I bought?
What watch?
The one I bought for you
when I went to Seoraksan Mountain
with the ladies.
FULL OF HAPPINESS
SEORAKSAN MOUNTAIN
I don't remember where I put it.
Kyeong-do!
Have you seen this small and round thing
by chance?
When you open it, there's a watch inside.
This small? Round?
Yes, did you see it?
A watch looks like that?
Jeez, you need to read more.
It's the kind of watch from the story,
The Gift of the Magi.
The one you can put
inside the pocket of your suit.
Oh, the story
where the wife cuts her hair
to buy a new chain?
Have you seen it or not?
No.
That's strange.
Did a petty thief steal it or what?
I know it's tough.
Whether I drink or take pills,
mind your own business.
Hey.
You should stop getting involved
with Seo Ji-woo.
Some people don't know when to stop.
Like Ji-woo and Kyeong-do.
Hey…
I keep coming back here,
but you're not here anymore.
Being sweet in a grumpy way.
The worried look in your eyes.
I keep imagining things.
If you stop me again,
that means you're also confused.